copperhq.com 2017-03-18

# Privacy Policy – CopperProject.com

Element Software takes your privacy and the security of your information very seriously. In fact our business depends on it. Here is a full disclosure regarding how we protect and use your information.

### What information do we collect?

  * We collect information from you when you use our website, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or place an order.
  * When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

### What do we use your information for?

  * Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 
    * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
    * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
    * To process transactions (Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service.)
    * To send periodic emails
  * The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
  * Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

### How do we protect your information?

  * We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.
  * We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.
  * Use of the Copper Service itself is available via SSL technology.
  * After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

### Do we use cookies?

  * Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information
  * We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

  * We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

  * Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
  * As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all subscribers to the Copper service may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘Edit Profile’ page.

### Terms and Conditions

  * Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at<http://www.copperproject.com/termsandconditions.php>

### Your Consent

  * By using our site, you consent to our [web site privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

  * If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
  * This policy was last modified on 08/21/12

### Contacting Us

    * If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

> http://www.copperproject.com  
>  PO BOX 596  
>  Yarraville, Victoria 3013  
>  Australia  
>  info@copperproject.com
